I'm in a courtroom, cold and grey. She's on the
left side, across the way. A lawyer spinning
twisted lies about the boy, he's
incapacitated. A captive who's been
manipulated. But then, the night... Shark
begins to rise. She stands and speaks her voice
clear. Your honor, there's no captive here.
He's a competent adult with a 4.0 result. Deans,
a transcript in her hand Self-elocusy, he took a
stand A wall of facts, a wall of proof It's
tearing off her broken roof And in the back, my
family Sixteen strong, all here for me This
isn't a fight, it's a release She has no case
The judge's eyes, they turn to me. Son, do you
feel you are not free? I look at her, my voice is
strong. I'm safer than I've ever been. This is
the only family that I have ever known or seen.
Transcript in her hand. Self-advocacy, he took
a stand. A wall of facts, a wall of proof. It's
tearing off a broken roof. And in the back, This
is not a case of incapacity. This is apparent.
who can't let go.
This petition is a waste of this court's time.
You are dangerously close to legal harassment.
Dismissed. With prejudice!
A transcript in her hand Saw the look, I see he
took a stand A wall of facts, a wall of proof It's
tearing up a broken roof And in the back, my
family Sixteen strong, all here for me This
isn't a fight, it's a release She has no case
She has no case
Dismissed
With prejudice